winndixie.com 2008-12-17

# Winn-Dixie Privacy Policy :: Protecting Your Right to Privacy : Winn-Dixie supports the consumer’s right to privacy Winn-Dixie Supermarket - Grocery Stores, Weekly Ads, Online Pharmacy, Liquor Stores, Grocery Store Coupons, Buy One Get One Free Offers, Recipes

## Our Commitment to Privacy

Winn-Dixie supports the consumer's right to privacy. We pledge never to knowingly loan, sell, rent or otherwise make available any personally identifiable information to third parties who intend to exploit the information for purposes unrelated to Winn-Dixie's business.

This notice was developed to help better protect your privacy by explaining our online information practices and to inform you of the choices you have about the way your information is collected and used. This notice is specific to the WinnDixie. com and WinnDixie.com websites only. To make this notice easy to find, we have placed a link at the bottom of our website's pages. 

## The Information We Collect and How it is Used

**Information You Provide Us**  
While using our websites, you may provide us with information when you place an order online, register with our website, submit a comment through our online comment form, enter an online sweepstakes, submit a resume, apply for a Customer Reward Card online, request a replacement Customer Reward Card online, update your Customer Reward Card information online, or enroll in a Reward Club online. The types of information that may be collected on these pages include:

  * **Your name** \- to personalize communications to you

  * **Your address** \- to contact you in response to comments or orders you submit, send you orders you've placed, forward any prizewinners documentation for online sweepstakes you have entered, as well as send you special offers if you choose to receive communication from us.

  * **Your phone number** \- to contact you in response to comments, orders, and sweepstakes entries that you submit

  * **Your e-mail address** \- to contact you in response to comments or orders you submit, or to send you special offers via e-mail if you choose to receive communication from us. Your Customer Reward Card number - to provide you with personalized offers and allow entry into online sweepstakes.

  * **Your credit/debit card information** \- to process orders placed online.

  * **Your baby's name and gender** (Baby Rewards Club enrollment only) - to personalize communications or offerings for your baby.

  * **Your baby's birth date** (Baby Rewards Club enrollment only) - to provide you with age-appropriate materials and offers.

These are in addition to any other information you provide us. This information may also be used to provide you with newsletters, magazines, coupons, special offers, to improve customer service, maintain proper inventories, lower costs, and to create special merchandising and marketing programs for shoppers who desire to participate.

There are also sections of the website where you may submit information about someone else. For example, if you order a gift card online and would like it delivered to another recipient, we would need to collect the following information about the recipient:

  * **Recipient's name** \- _to properly address the recipient of the gift._

  * **Recipient's address** \- _to ship the gift to._

  * **Recipient's phone number** \- _to notify the recipient in case of delivery problems._

**Anonymous Information**  
This type of information is collected on all visitors to our web site, but is not used to identify individual customers. Anonymous information may include aggregate information of the number of customers utilizing different services on our web site, as well as the frequency of their visits. We may then use this information to help improve the hardware and/or software that runs on our site.

**IP Addresses**  
If you utilize one of our online forms to submit comments or an application to us, Winn-Dixie.com or WinnDixie.com may collect information that includes your Internet provider's (IP) address, the type and version of your web browser. By analyzing this type of information, we can more easily diagnose problems with our site as well as provide a means to monitor traffic throughout the site. This type of information does not contain any personally identifiable information.

**Cookies**  
In an effort to provide a more enhanced and customized experience while browsing Winn-Dixie.com, Winn-Dixie may place a "cookie" on your computer when you visit our site. A cookie is a unique set of data assigned to only you and placed in a text file that is stored on your computer. Since cookies are text files, they cannot "run" nor track your usage of other Web sites or the Internet.

Using cookies allows Winn-Dixie.com and WinnDixie.com to "remember" what it has done for you, and to keep track of information that you may have provided to Winn-Dixie.com or WinnDixie.com. Among other things, Winn-Dixie.com and WinnDixie.com may use these cookies to display promotions and events that are unique to your geographical location, remember your Customer Reward Card number so you don't have to enter it each time you visit our site, and remember the store you tell us you shop at most to make it even more convenient to get your store's ad circulars online.

Under the "Help" menu of most browser toolbars, you may find information on how to prevent your browser from accepting cookies or how to notify you if a site is trying to write a cookie to your site. However, cookies enable you to take full advantage of some of the great features on our website, so we recommend that you leave them turned on.

## What Choices Do You Have?

You may choose not to receive communications from us by either mail or e-mail by simply updating your preferences on your Customer Reward Card application or by unsubscribing to an e-mail that you may receive. To change your communications preferences on your Customer Reward Card application, please select "Update Information" under the "Reward Card" section on the left column of the website, then complete your information and click the button next to "No, don't send me mailings about unadvertised specials or personal offers." You may also call us at **1-866-WINN-DIXIE (1866- 946-6349).**

## Sharing With Other Companies

Winn-Dixie Stores, Inc. may provide personally identifiable information to outside vendors for analysis, verification, revision, consolidation or storage, but only to enable Winn-Dixie to use the information more effectively in serving its customers. We may also provide this information to regulatory, law enforcement or other governmental entities upon proper request. Under an appropriate contract, Winn-Dixie may make personally identifiable information available to a third party so the third party may join with or assist Winn-Dixie in providing promotions or services to our customers. In any case, Winn-Dixie does not make personally identifiable information available to a third party (other than a governmental entity) unless it has entered into a contract with Winn-Dixie that requires it to maintain security procedures to prevent unauthorized access to the information.

It is not unusual for companies to consolidate their operations in new corporate structures, to merge with other corporations, or to transfer ownership of a business unit so that it can continue to function under a new owner. Winn-Dixie pledges that it will never transfer your personally identifiable information to such a new owner or corporate entity except under a contract that requires the new owner or entity to continue to abide by our promises to you above. Winn-Dixie is not obligated to observe the above restrictions when providing non-personally identifiable compilations of information to third parties.

## Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy whenever children are involved. Winn-Dixie.com and WinnDixie.com does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

## Our Commitment to Data Security

Winn-Dixie Stores, Inc. maintains strict security procedures, including physical, electronic and managerial, to prevent unauthorized access to personal information.

Our website uses Secure Socket Layering (SSL) to encrypt your credit information, including your credit card number, before it is transferred over the Internet. Because we use SSL, you can be confident that your online order is as safe as placing a credit card order over the phone.

## Links To or From Other Websites

Winn-Dixie.com or WinnDixie.com may offer links to other websites not owned or operated by Winn-Dixie Stores, Inc. These web sites have their own policies regarding Privacy and Terms of Use. If you visit one of these web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policy on their site.

## Privacy Policy Changes

This privacy statement was last updated on Winn-Dixie.com and WinnDixie.com on September 29, 2004. Winn-Dixie Stores, Inc. reserves the right to change, modify or append this policy at any time, so we encourage you to review it periodically.

## Questions

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please feel free to [contact us.](http://winn-dixie.com/Contact_Us)
